Ngan Ha

Shine Group

353C Nguyen Trong Tuyen, Ward 01, Tan Binh District, HCM

Dear Madam,

I am interested in applying for the RA executive at Shine Group. I clearly understand that my background and experience do not make me an eligible candidate for your consideration.

I have got knowledge about circulars, especially about registration and obtainment of material's license for the required business (focus on import ingredients from foreign contry into Vietnam which is main task of Shine Group). In addition, I had trained about GPs and understand GDP/GSP guidelines. Athough I have no experience in this field before, I have confidence in my professional skills as well as my knowledge which I gained in university. So that I could work as a RA executive.

I hope to have an opportunity to talk with you in person. I live in Hue city but I am willing to relocate to Ho Chi Minh city. Please find my number and email in my curriculum vitae. I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Hy Nguyen



Nguyen Thi Dieu Hy

10/09/1995

Objectives

- Working in a dynamic and challenging environment.
 Willing to learn and enhance the professionality.
- Five-year goal: Become a teamleader and lead the team to become a cadre of the company.

Education

- Hue University of Medicine and Pharmacy 2013-2018
 Major in Pharmacy Score: 7.32
- Certificate in Applied Informatics Technology
- TOEIC certificate

Skills

- Strong at Microsoft Office.
- Read comprehension pharmaceutical document, basic communicate via English.
- Make plans and work well in a team.

Hobbies

- Reading book
- Travelling and exploring
- Taking photos

Activities

2016-2018

• 2016 - 2018: Clinical Pharmacy Club

- Be an active member in club.
- Improve presentation skill through activities in the club. Look for information and translate pharmaceutical document.

2016: Scientific Research

- Do the research "Study of plant characteristics of Asclepias curassavica L. Apocynaceae" under direct supervision of Master Tran Thi Thuy Linh.
- Develope skills about find specialized materials, do microsurgery of stem and leaf, write scientific research reports.

Experience

2016-2018

• 2016 - 2018: Tutor

- Learn the way to transfer knowledge. Prepare lectures which are suitable for each students.

2017 - 2018: Translation

- Translate package inserts from English to Vietnamese.
- Enhance vocabulary, expande knowledge about treatment drug, understand drug use and addition.

2018: Internship at Medipharco Tenamyd JSC

- Learn about manufacture follow GMP procedures: ingredients in warehouses become final products through engineering department.
- Understand the SOP for warehouse department: receipt and storage material, environmental controll and monitoring...
- Get used to tasks in QA, QC, business, pharmacies and R&D department (investigation and completion of new product, technology transfer process).

• 2018: Internship at Hue University hospital

- Practice at outpatient pharmacies: participate in dispensing drugs to patients and provide medication advice.
- Practice at drug warehouses of hospital: dispensing drugs to inpatient departments, arrange medical products, do monthly inventory.